cbproads.com 2013-09-22

# Privac Policy of Clickbank Pro Ads.com (CbProAds.com)

|   
---  
| **

Clickbank Ad Rotator

** | ** ****

**Clickbank Storefronts  
(Affiliate)**

** | ** **

**Clickbank Niche Storefronts  
(Affiliate)**

 | ** **

**Clickbank Storefronts  
(WordPress based)**

 | ** **

**Clickbank Niche Storefronts  
(WordPress based)**

---|---|---|---|---  
  
|   
---  
  
28th Jul 2013   
9 more niche storefronts have been added for you as part of our service. Please [click here](http://cbproads.com/clickbank_niche_storefront_wordpress_plugin.asp) to know more about them. ********

**  
**

** 26th Jun 2013   
We will have a major change in design of the overall website. Here is the demo link. [CBproads new design.](http://prismitsolutions.com/demo/HTML/cbproads/)** ****

**

7th Apr 2013   
An another attention grabbibg tool has been added (Sliding Boxes) which you can place on to your website/blog. [**Click here for a demo**](http://www.cbproads.com/banner_demo.asp) ********

**

4th Feb 2013   
More improved dynamics have been to existing banner ads. And so it displays up to 7 ads in one block itself instead of previous one. Please check the demo at i.e [**CBProads.com/banner_demo.asp**](http://www.cbproads.com/banner_demo.asp) ********

**

25th Jan 2013   
We have officially released the latest one to our collection of niche storefronts i.e [**Water For Fuel Conversion Guides**](http://waterforfuel-guides.com/?id=15750) ********

**  
**

** 24th Sep 2012   
The much awaited **Wordpress plugin for clickbank niche storefronts** will be released on 26th Sep 2012. Now you can install the script on to your website and have full control rather than **Clickbank affiliate niche storefronts**.** ****

**  

6th Sep 2011   
Clickbank Niche Storefronts have been released. **Click here** for an online demo.

16th Jan 2011   
The Storefront Version 4.0 has been released. **Click here** for a online demo.

18th Nov 2010   
iPhone Widget Ads has been introduced to the ads section. **Click here** to see it live.

********  
  
|   
---  
|    
---  
Privacy Policy  
   
We are committed to protecting your privacy and the security of information you provide to us. CBproADS will not sell, rent, lease or disclose customer information to third parties unless required by law or unless you provide consent to such a disclosure. Other terms of CBproADS' privacy policy are as follows:   
   
Information Collection   
When you engage in activities on our website or within our services, like registering, using trial versions of services, requesting technical support, or subscribing to newsletters and e-mail publications, CBproADS may ask you to provide us with information. 

By choosing to enter and submit the requested information when prompted, you are consenting to CBproADS' collection, use, and disclosure of such information for the purposes of providing the services to you as outlined herein. 

Any information you post to our live customer support chat window is available to all staffs of the site.   

How We Use Your Information   
Any information collected will be used only by CBproADS to improve our services and website, or to communicate with you in the form of newsletters and notices if you give us permission to do so. CBproADS uses information and/or e-mail addresses for internal purposes only and does not sell, lease or rent information to third parties.   
   
Choice/Opt-In/Opt-Out   
This site allows visitors to unsubscribe so that they will not receive future messages. After unsubscribing we will discontinue sending the particular messages as soon as technically feasible.   
   
Acquisition or Changes in Ownership   
In the event that the web site (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, your information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred.   
   
Policy Modifications   
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when changes are made to this privacy policy, we will email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.   

|  |  |   
---|---|---
